♪
Hello. - Hello.
Yes, ma'am.
Well...
I've been very grateful lately.
I'm very grateful to the many people
I'm glad that you know a lot about us.
Well, to newcomers
I would like more members to get to know each other,
I would like you to know more about our members,
I would like to answer 100 questions.
First of all, I, Hikaru Irizuki, will answer the first question. I, Hikaru Irizuki, will answer the first one.
Please do so.
Yes, I am Hikaru Rizuki from Akita.
My name is Hikaru Rizuki from Akita Prefecture.
My member color is pure white.
As for my nickname, my official nickname is Hikaru, so my good friends call me Lun-chan.
My birthday is July 31, 2001.
I think I will listen to Snow Magic Fantasy on the day the world ends!
Mr. End of the World
Yakitori and Bonjiri!
I like them both, but maybe the sauce.
I won't go to all that trouble.
Fatton Twintail.
I like it a little higher.
I like rubber.
I don't know about men.
I don't care what it is.
White. He wants to be an angel, so he's going for white.
I kind of don't want to believe it.
And cod roe?
The smooth one.
And about 82.
Scissors to cut bangs and books and switches I don't always have time to do, I tend to take pretty much everything with me.
Harmonica.
It's a hassle, so I eat it as it is. The dream I had recently was...I eat it as it is because it's a pain in the ass.
I dreamed recently that I was in a building with a glass wall.
I was in this building, and the building across the street had glass walls.
The building across the street has a glass wall.
I dreamed that a macho man was filming there.
a macho man was filming.
Summer
Rice
Pork bone
Shrimp anywhere, please
Shrimp anywhere, please!
Shrimp
Izumi Pink
Candy Babies
I have a lot of favorite words.
But my favorite right now is
Let's see...
I don't care if they're different from each other or not
I want to go to Ishikawa Prefecture
Paris and London
I want to go to Paris because it's normal.
I want to go to London.
Sherlock Holmes, I've always loved Harry Potter, so I want to go there.
I always go when my friends invite me.
The rest of the time I sleep.
I'm sleeping now.
Rabbit
I especially like rabbits with floppy ears.
And unicorns.
and Shiro Pome.
I like all of them, but I especially like
I like all of them, but I especially like Mixed Juice.
Q. What is your favorite type of picture?
What is your favorite lyric?
Tinkle
BabyBaby
Angel
and Moon.
Q. How tall were you when you were working?
Q. How tall were you when you were active?
I think I was in the 9s when I was active. Q. What are your morals?
Q. What are your morals?
Q. What do you drink?
Q. What do you like to drink the most?
Q. What do you like best?
Phantom
Q.What is your highest price? Phantom
The highest is Wow!
This is the low one.
Wow, this one.
I have a habit
I want to get dressed and fall in love.
I want to put on clothes and fall in love
I want to put on clothes and fall in love.
I'm glad I thought of that.
It's fun... but basically, I feel it.
I feel, not think, but feel
I want to feel, not think
I want to be in love with happiness
And then there's
fireworks
is my favorite, so that's fun too!
I also like songs that don't lose
Enoki and so on.
Q.What character do you like?
Q.What kind of character do you like?
A.Well, I like the devil master star Butterfly.
Q.What character do you like?
A.Tokio.
Q.What character do you like? A. Tokio
Miyu-chan.Miyu and Kaya?
Q. What kind of person do you like?
Shinju-chan!
Please!
Q. What kind of sports do you want to play?
Let's see...
Uni-pace sports are...
Well... let's see...
If I had the ability, I'd like to play soccer.
Um, yeah, but I don't think I want either.
Height?
Hello! It's a beautiful day!
I'm in love with clothes... once and for all.
Yes, well...
Well, I think I'd like to be above the clouds.
Q. What color do you like?
A.Baby pink.
Q.What is your latest item?
A.I wonder...
A.Hmmm...
A. Recently, um, a while ago..,
Something like, um, I bought a switch in secret...is that high? Recently.
Q. How many switches have you bought?
The largest amount?
I haven't done that many,
I was sad, and then I got up,
I was in a state of grief, and my body woke up, and I was like, "Is it a boy? I was like, "Oh my gosh!
The scariest story is that I heard a cry like "oh my god!
Q. Who is the scariest idol you have ever seen?
Arako?
Q. Who was the scariest of all your idols?
Well, let's see...Hmmm... I guess so.
Eh, there are many things I would like to do, but I would like to work with comedians and stuff.
I take a little picture, and then later when I'm eating, I swallow it, and it grows out of here, and then I grow it, and then I eat it again, and repeat.
I thought that if a girl and a boy could twirl and fall over together, that would be marriage.
67 years old.
I don't know.
What? Is that right?
Yes, it is. When I was little.
I liked to read books all the time.
I also liked to write poems on manuscript paper and give them to my mother.
See? See?
Hmmm...
I don't know.
If anything...
It's cute, but...
It's like the light is going to shine through it.
I'd like to remove it. How did you like it?
A lemon that's a dream come true.
I've been jumping up and down.
[fast forward]
Thank you, thank you.
He's sleeping.
[fast forward]
Caramel Popcorn and Kalopis Koliskolamen
Fast Forward] First of all, when I was in elementary school, I was in the track team and I was a high jumper.
I was not athletic at all,
I had no choice but to join the basketball team, the track team, the instrumental team, or the small team.
I had no choice but to join the basketball team, track and field, musical instruments, or small.
When I was in junior high school, I was in the volleyball club.
I joined the volleyball club in junior high school because my older sister was in it.
In high school, I joined the tea ceremony club at first, but quit halfway through.
Are they difficult songs?
Well, all of them are difficult, but the symphony one is very difficult because of the hamoris.
I'm doing the hamoris.
Q. What kind of harmonies do you do?
Let's see,Let's see,
Hmmm,
When I was in the first grade of junior high school,
I was scouted by Starlast in Tokyo,
At that time, there was no Sendai office yet, so I turned it down.
And about a year later, I went to Akita to work at Uion.
I was escorted by the current manager and captain
I was given a skirt by the current manager and captain.
My mom was in the same office.
I said, "It's fate.
and I was accepted.
Q.Did you choose the skirt yourself? Of course. Q. What is your favorite color? I had them put it in for me.
Of course.
I sometimes watch my favorite You Tuber Han- something like that.
I sometimes watch them.
I don't know...
YouTubers
It's more like a comedian's
You Tube or something.
of comedians rather than youtubers.
I also like Ochiyurana a lot.
I watch Ochiyurana's youtube and so on.
Seiko is addicted to
I was addicted to watching chicks grow up with my grandma.
There are so many chicks nearby,
I was addicted to watching them grow up.
What are your grandma's hobbies?
Well, she was dangerous.
What are her hobbies?
Well...
Getting compliments.
And watching American comedies.
and watching comedy.
Matsuba
Definitely pine needles, definitely waiting!
No, but I could swim 25 meters when I was healthy.No, but I could swim 25 meters when I was healthy.
Mmm, yes.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
I'm a lot of things.
I don't know.
You know, where there's a lot of white rice and stuff.
I keep going there, but it's hard to get hired.
Yes I like both. Both...
Macarons
Budokan
Um... Misaki Narumi
Narumi Misaki Narumi Misaki Budokan
Um, round-eared rabbit
White, wide
Um, well, first of all, Rine is a high-class cat.
And, Yuna is a Yuna sounding neck-branch,
Mariya is a bear,
I wonder what Kabayashi-kun is.
I wonder what Kalin-kun is, Shimae-san or something.
And Minana is a little girl.
And Miyu-chan is a..,
Squirrel.
And Kaya is a lion.
That's right.
Hmmm...
The part where we joke around in earnest.
Eh.
Seiko Oi.
Hey, right? But it's embarrassing.
Kana?
But I want to.
Yes, I do.
Fortune teller.
Let's see...
Macarons.Macarons
Well, where they do the whole process.
Where they do the front and back.
Where they sometimes go to different idols or something... that's fine.
Chupero
You know, where everyone gets along well with each other.
To be together.
Chupero
Chupero Deluxe
Japara Deluxe Japara Deluxe!
It was fun. I don't know,
I'm sorry for being so random.
But it was a lot of fun.
Did you get to know Nou-chan?
Please look forward to the next members!
Thanks for watching, bunny!
Bye, bye, bye!
you